Anthony Lewis Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part II: Annual File, 1949-2007 (Box II:1-843)
  - 1984
    - Bylines
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Middle East, (2 folders)
      - New Yorker, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box II:266)
    - "B" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - California
    - Cambodia
    - Capital punishment, (3 folders) (Box II:267)
    - Carter, Jimmy
    - Central Intelligence Agency
    - China
    - Committee to Protect Journalists
    - Congress, (2 folders)
    - Courts, (2 folders)
    - "C" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:268)
    - Defense
      - Chemical and biological weapons
      - Nuclear weapons, (4 folders)
    - Defense and disarmament
    - Dunne, Philip
    - "D" miscellaneous (Box II:269)
    - Economy, (2 folders)
    - Education
    - "E" miscellaneous
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - Food
    - Fund for Free Expression, (3 folders)
    - "F" miscellaneous
    - Great Britain
    - Grenville Clark Fund (Box II:270)
    - "G" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Hart, Gary
    - Harvard Crimson
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Human rights, (2 folders)
    - "H" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - India (Box II:271)
    - Ireland
    - "I" miscellaneous
    - Jackson, Jesse
    - "J" miscellaneous
    - Kennedy, Edward M.
    - Khalidi, Walid, (2 folders)
    - Kissinger, Henry
    - KQED-TV, San Francisco, Calif.
    - "K" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Latin America (Box II:272)
      - Chile
      - Cuba
      - El Salvador, (5 folders)
      - General
      - Grenada, (2 folders)
      - Guatemala, (2 folders) (Box II:273)
      - Nicaragua, (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:274)
    - Law
      - Disability, (5 folders)
      - General
    - "L" miscellaneous
    - Massachusetts
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, Boston, Mass. (Box II:275)
    - Meese, Edwin, (3 folders)
    - Middle East
      - Egypt
      - General, (4 folders)
      - Israel, press briefs, (2 folders) (Box II:276)
      - Jerusalem
      - Jordan
      - Lebanon, (3 folders)
      - Palestine Liberation Organization
      - Syria
      - Trip
      - West Bank
    - Mondale, Walter F. (Box II:277)
    - Murdoch, Rupert
    - "M" miscellaneous
    - New York
    - New York Times
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Staff, (3 folders)
    - Nieman Foundation, (2 folders)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box II:278)
    - "N" miscellaneous
    - Obscenity
    - "O" miscellaneous
    - Philippines
    - Poland
    - Politics
      - Democratic National Convention, (3 folders)
      - General, (3 folders)
    - Press (Box II:279)
      - Branzburg v. Hayes, (3 folders)
      - Freedom of Information Act
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Great Britain, (2 folders)
      - Libel and privacy (Box II:280)
        - General, (6 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:281, Box II:282)
        - Sharon v. Time, Inc., (5 folders)
        - Westmoreland v. Columbia Broadcasting System, (4 folders) (Box II:283)
      - Pentagon Papers
      - Snepp v. United States
    - "P" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - "Q" miscellaneous (Box II:284)
    - Race
    - Reagan, Ronald, (4 folders)
    - Religion, (3 folders)
    - "R" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:285)
    - Sakharov, Andrei
    - Secrecy
    - Soviet Union, (4 folders)
    - Smith, William French, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box II:286)
    - Speeches
      - Jan.-Apr., (4 folders)
      - May, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:287)
      - June-Dec., (7 folders)
    - Supreme Court, (2 folders) (Box II:288)
    - Surroundings
    - "S-U" miscellaneous, (5 folders)
    - Vietnam, (2 folders)
    - "V-W" miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box II:289)
    - Yugoslavia, (2 folders)
    - "Y-Z" miscellaneous
  - 1985
    - Abortion, (2 folders)
    - Africa
      - Angola, (2 folders)
      - Ethiopia
      - General
      - Mozambique, (2 folders) (Box II:290)
      - Namibia
      - South Africa
        - Disinvestment, (6 folders)
        - General, (7 folders); (6 folders) (Box II:291, Box II:292)
        - Health, (3 folders)
        - Law, (2 folders) (Box II:293)
        - Massacre
        - Nightline, (2 folders)
        - State of emergency, (3 folders)
      - Zimbabwe
    - "A" miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box II:294)
    - Book reviews, (4 folders)
    - Boston, Mass.
    - Brennan, William J.
    - Bylines, (2 folders)
    - "B" miscellaneous, (7 folders) (Box II:295)
    - California, (2 folders)
    - Cambodia (Box II:296)
    - Capital punishment, (2 folders)
    - Carter, Jimmy
    - Central Intelligence Agency, (2 folders)
    - China
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Trip
        - Background material, (2 folders)
        - Correspondence
        - General, (5 folders) (Box II:297)
        - Maps
        - Names and telephone numbers
        - Notes, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box II:298)
        - Pamphlets
        - Photographs
    - Clubs
    - Colby College, Waterville, Maine
    - Committee to Protect Journalists, (2 folders) (Box II:299)
    - Constitution
      - American Bar Association, (4 folders)
      - General, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box II:300)
    - Courts, (2 folders)
    - Crime
    - "C" miscellaneous, (4 folders)
    - Defense (Box II:301)
      - Chemical and biological weapons
      - Nuclear weapons
        - General, (5 folders)
        - Treaties, (2 folders)
    - Defense and disarmament
    - "D" miscellaneous, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:302)
    - Economy
    - "E" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation, (2 folders)
    - Food
    - Fund for Free Expression, (2 folders)
    - "F" miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box II:303)
    - Great Britain, (2 folders)
    - Grenville Clark Fund
    - "G" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Harvard Crimson
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Human rights
      - East Timor
      - General, (2 folders) (Box II:304)
    - "H" miscellaneous, (4 folders)
    - International Design Conference, Aspen, Colo.
    - Iran
    - Ireland
    - Japan, trip, (3 folders); (4 folders) (Box II:305)
    - "J" miscellaneous
    - Kennedy, Edward M.
    - Kennedy, Robert F.
    - Kirkpatrick, Jeane J., (2 folders)
    - Korea
    - "K" miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box II:306)
    - Latin America
      - Chile
      - El Salvador, (5 folders)
      - General
      - Guatemala
      - Honduras
      - Nicaragua, (8 folders) (Box II:307)
    - Law (Box II:308)
      - Disability, (3 folders)
      - General
    - "L" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Massachusetts
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, Boston, Mass.
    - Meese, Edwin, (2 folders) (Box II:309)
    - Middle East
      - Finkelstein, Norman G., (4 folders)
      - General, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:310)
      - Hamdan, Hussein
      - Israel, press briefs
      - Jordan
      - Lebanon
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Hostages, (2 folders)
      - West Bank
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., (3 folders)
    - "M" miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box II:311)
    - New York, (2 folders)
    - New York Times
      - Frankel, Max
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Staff, (3 folders)
      - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs (Box II:312)
    - Nieman Foundation
    - Nixon, Richard M.
    - "N" miscellaneous
    - Obscenity
    - "O" miscellaneous
    - Pakistan
    - Philippines
    - Politics
    - Press
      - Branzburg v. Hayes
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Great Britain, (2 folders)
      - Lakian v. Globe Newspaper Co. (Box II:313)
      - Libel and privacy
        - General, (7 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:314)
        - Tavoulareas v. Piro, (3 folders)
        - Westmoreland v. Columbia Broadcasting System, (3 folders)
      - Murdoch, Rupert
      - Snepp v. United States and United States v. Marchetti
      - United States v. Morison, (1 folder) (Box II:315)
    - "P" miscellaneous
    - Race, (3 folders)
    - Reagan, Ronald
      - Bitburg, Germany, visit, (2 folders)
      - Buchanan, Patrick J.
      - Economy, (1 folder) (Box II:316)
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Summit with the Soviet Union, Geneva, Switzerland, (2 folders)
    - Religion, (2 folders)
    - Right (political conservatism)
    - "R" miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box II:317)
    - Safer, Morley
    - Secrecy, (2 folders)
    - Shultz, George Pratt
    - Soviet Union
      - General
      - John Paul II, Pope (Box II:318)
      - Rights, (4 folders)
    - Speeches
      - Jan.-Feb., (4 folders)
      - Mar.-Dec., (11 folders) (Box II:319)
    - Supreme Court, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:320)
    - Surroundings, (2 folders)
    - "S" miscellaneous, (5 folders)
    - Television (Box II:321)
    - Tobacco, (2 folders)
    - Turkey
    - "T" miscellaneous
    - United Nations
    - "U" miscellaneous
    - Vietnam, (3 folders)
    - "V" miscellaneous
    - "W" miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box II:322)
    - Yugoslavia, (2 folders)
    - "Y-Z" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
  - 1986
    - Afghanistan
    - Africa
      - Angola, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:323)
      - Ethiopia
      - General
      - Liberia
      - Morocco
      - Mozambique
      - Namibia
      - Nigeria
      - South Africa
        - African National Congress
        - Children, (5 folders)
        - Disinvestment, (5 folders) (Box II:324)
        - Ford Foundation, (2 folders)
        - General, (4 folders); (7 folders) (Box II:325)
        - Health
        - Labor
        - Law (Box II:326)
        - Press
        - State of emergency, (5 folders)
        - Transkei
        - United States
      - Zimbabwe (Box II:327)
    - Asia
    - "A" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Blackmun, Harry A.
    - Book reviews, (2 folders)
    - Boston, Mass., (2 folders)
    - Boston University, Boston, Mass.
    - Brennan, William J.
    - Bylines, (3 folders) (Box II:328)
    - "B" miscellaneous, (6 folders); (3 folders) (Box II:329)
    - California, (5 folders)
    - Capital punishment
    - Carter, Jimmy
    - Central Intelligence Agency (Box II:330)
    - China
    - Committee to Protect Journalists, (3 folders)
    - Congress
    - Constitution
      - Bicentennial, (2 folders) (Box II:331)
      - General, (5 folders)
    - Courts, (2 folders) (Box II:332)
    - Crime
    - Czechoslovakia
    - "C" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Defense, nuclear weapons
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Strategic Defense Initiative, (2 folders) (Box II:333)
      - Test
      - Treaty
    - Defense and disarmament, (2 folders)
    - Drugs
    - "D" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Economy (Box II:334)
      - General
      - Trade
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
    - "E" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation, (2 folders)
    - Food
    - Free speech
    - Freud, Anna, (2 folders) (Box II:335)
    - Fund for Free Expression
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Haase, Edward, (2 folders)
    - "F" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Great Britain (Box II:336)
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Trip
    - "G" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Harvard Crimson, (2 folders)
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box II:337)
    - Health
    - Human rights
      - East Timor, (2 folders)
      - General
    - "H" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:338)
    - Immigration, (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:339)
    - International Design Conference, Aspen Colo.
    - Iran-Contra Affair, (6 folders)
    - Iraq
    - Italy
      - General
      - Trip, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:340)
    - "I" miscellaneous
    - Japan, (2 folders)
    - "J" miscellaneous
    - Kennedy, Edward M.
    - Kennedy, Joseph P., II
    - Kimball, Penn, (2 folders)
    - Kissinger, Henry
    - "K" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Latin America (Box II:341)
      - Chile, (3 folders)
      - Ecuador
      - El Salvador
      - General
      - Grenada
      - Guatemala, (2 folders)
      - Honduras
      - Nicaragua, (2 folders); (8 folders) (Box II:342)
    - Law (Box II:343)
      - Disability
      - General, (5 folders)
    - "L" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Massachusetts (Box II:344)
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, Boston, Mass.
    - Meese, Edwin
    - Middle East
      - Civil liberties
      - Finkelstein, Norman G., (2 folders)
      - General, (2 folders)
      - International Center for Peace in the Middle East, Tel Aviv, Israel
      - Libya, (2 folders) (Box II:345)
      - Palestinian Liberation Organization
      - West Bank
    - "M" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - New Israel Fund, (2 folders)
    - New York, (2 folders) (Box II:346)
    - New York Times
      - Frankel, Max
      - General
      - Klein, Edward
      - Staff, (3 folders)
      - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs
    - Nieman Foundation
    - Nixon, Richard M.
    - "N" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Obscenity (Box II:347)
    - "O" miscellaneous
    - Pakistan
    - Peretz, Martin
    - Philippines, (2 folders)
    - Press
      - Branzburg v. Hayes
      - Contempt
      - General
      - Great Britain, (2 folders)
      - Libel (Box II:348)
        - General, (5 folders)
        - King v. Globe Newspaper Co., (2 folders) (Box II:349)
        - New Yorker, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:350)
        - Sharon v. Time, Inc., (3 folders)
        - Speeches
      - Morison, Samuel Loring
      - Privacy, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:351)
      - United States v. Marchetti and Snepp v. United States, (2 folders)
    - Politics
      - Cuomo, Mario M.
      - Flynn, Raymond
      - General
      - Helms, Jesse
      - Jackson, Jesse
      - Simon, Paul
    - "P-Q" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Race, (2 folders) (Box II:352)
    - Reagan, Ronald
      - Economy
      - General, (4 folders)
      - Summit, (2 folders)
    - Redgrave, Vanessa, (5 folders) (Box II:353)
    - Rehnquist, William H., (5 folders) (Box II:354)
    - Right (political and religious), (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:355)
    - Romania
    - "R" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Scalia, Antonin, (2 folders)
    - Secrecy
    - Shultz, George Pratt
    - Soviet Union
      - General, (1 folder) (Box II:356)
      - Rights, (5 folders)
    - Space
    - Speech material
      - Brennan, William, J.
      - Foreign countries
      - General, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:357)
      - Mass ratification
      - Meese, Edwin, (2 folders)
    - Speeches
      - Jan., (3 folders)
      - Feb.-Mar.
      - Mar., (8 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:358, Box II:359)
      - Apr.-July, (2 folders)
      - Oct., (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:360)
      - Nov.-Dec., (3 folders)
    - Supreme Court, (2 folders)
    - Surroundings
    - Sweden
    - "S" miscellaneous, (5 folders) (Box II:361)
    - Tax
    - Television, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:362)
    - Tobacco
    - Turkey
    - "T-V" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Waldheim, Kurt, (3 folders)
    - "W" miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box II:363)
    - Yale University, New Haven, Conn.
    - Yugoslavia
    - "Y-Z" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
  - 1987
    - Afghanistan, (2 folders)
    - Africa
      - Angola
      - Botswana (Box II:364)
        - General, (4 folders)
        - Tsetse fly
      - General
      - Mozambique, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:365)
      - Namibia
      - South Africa
        - African National Congress, (2 folders)
        - Disinvestment, (3 folders)
        - Farisani, Tshenuweni Simon
        - Ford Foundation, (2 folders)
        - General, (1 folder); (8 folders) (Box II:366)
        - Health
        - Labor
        - Law (Box II:367)
        - Press, (2 folders)
        - State of emergency
        - Trip
        - United States
      - Zimbabwe
        - General
        - Trip, (2 folders)
    - Asia
    - Aspen, Colo.
    - "A" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:368)
    - Blackmun, Harry A.
    - Book reviews, (2 folders)
    - Bork, Robert H., nomination to the Supreme Court
      - Antitrust
      - Committee on the Judiciary, report
      - Documents about Bork's judicial record, (3 folders); (6 folders); (5 folders) (Box II:369, Box II:370)
      - Essays and reports, (2 folders) (Box II:371)
      - General, (3 folders); (7 folders) (Box II:372, Box II:373)
      - Notebooks of briefing material from Lloyd N. Cutler
        - Vol. 1, (3 folders)
        - Vol. 2, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:374)
      - Speeches by Bork, (2 folders)
      - Veto
    - Boston, Mass.
    - Brennan, William J.
    - Bylines
      - General, (2 folders)
      - New York Times Magazine, (2 folders) (Box II:375)
    - "B" miscellaneous, (4 folders)
    - California
    - Cambodia
    - Canada
    - Capital punishment
    - Carlucci, Frank Charles
    - Censorship, (2 folders) (Box II:376)
    - Central Intelligence Agency, (2 folders)
    - China, (2 folders)
    - Column ideas
    - Committee to Protect Journalists
    - Constitution
      - Bicentennial, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box II:377)
      - General, (3 folders) (Box II:378)
      - Television series, (2 folders)
    - Courts
    - Crime
    - "C" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Defense (Box II:379)
      - Chemical and biological weapons
      - General
      - Nuclear weapons
        - General, (2 folders)
        - Strategic Defense Initiative
        - Treaty, (2 folders)
    - "D" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Economy, (2 folders)
    - Elman, Philip, (2 folders) (Box II:380)
    - "E" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - Free speech
    - Fund for Free Expression
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Lara, Patricia (Box II:381)
    - "F" miscellaneous
    - Ginsburg, Douglas H., (4 folders)
    - Great Britain
      - Election, (2 folders)
      - General
      - Trips
    - "G" miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box II:382)
    - Harvard Crimson
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard Magazine
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Health
    - Horace Mann School, New York, N.Y.
    - Human rights
    - "H" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Immigration (Box II:383)
      - General, (4 folders)
      - Palestinians, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:384)
    - Iran-Contra Affair
      - Commentary
      - Congress, (2 folders)
      - General, (3 folders)
      - North, Oliver
      - Pardons
      - Reagan, Ronald
      - Special prosecutor, constitutionality of, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box II:385)
      - Tower Commission
    - Ireland
    - "I" miscellaneous
    - Japan
    - "J" miscellaneous
    - Kennedy, Anthony M., (1 folder) (Box II:386)
    - Kennedy, John F.
    - Korea
    - "K" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Latin America
      - Chile, (3 folders)
      - Cuba
      - El Salvador (Box II:387)
      - General
      - Grenada
      - Guatemala
      - Nicaragua
        - Aid to the Contras, (2 folders)
        - General, (6 folders)
    - Law, (3 folders) (Box II:388)
    - "L" miscellaneous, (4 folders)
    - Massachusetts
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, Boston, Mass.
    - Meese, Edwin, (2 folders)
    - Middle East (Box II:389)
      - General, (5 folders)
      - Israel, press briefs
      - Jordan
      - Palestine Liberation Organization
      - Syria
      - West Bank, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:390)
    - "M" miscellaneous, (4 folders)
    - New York Times
      - Frankel, Max
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Staff, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:391)
      - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs
    - "N" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Obscenity, (2 folders)
    - "O" miscellaneous
    - Pakistan
    - Poland
    - Politics
      - Babbitt, Bruce E.
      - Cuomo, Mario M.
      - Dole, Robert J.
      - Dukakis, Michael S., (1 folder) (Box II:392)
      - General
      - Hart, Gary, (3 folders)
      - Simon, Paul
    - Press
      - Branzburg v. Hayes
      - Freedom of Information Act
      - Gannett v. DePasquale, (2 folders)
      - General
      - Great Britain
        - General, (1 folder) (Box II:393)
        - Wright, Peter, (3 folders)
      - Libel
        - General, (4 folders)
        - Globe Newspaper Co. v. King (Box II:394)
        - Hustler Magazine, Inc. v. Falwell, (3 folders)
        - Immuno AG v. Moor-Jankowski, (3 folders); (5 folders) (Box II:395)
        - Laxalt v. McClatchy
        - Missing by Thomas C. Hauser, (1 folder) (Box II:396)
        - New Yorker
        - Tavoulareas v. Piro
      - Murdoch, Rupert
      - Privacy
      - Singapore
      - Snepp v. United States, (2 folders)
      - United States v. Morison
    - "P" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box II:397)
    - Race, (2 folders)
    - Reagan, Ronald
      - Buchanan, Patrick J.
      - General, (5 folders)
    - Rehnquist, William H. (Box II:398)
    - Religion
    - Right (political conservatism)
    - Romania
    - "R" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Scalia, Antonin
    - Shultz, George Pratt
    - Soviet Union
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Rights, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box II:399)
    - Speeches
      - Jan.-Mar., (5 folders)
      - Apr. 2-8
      - Apr. 15-23 (Box II:400)
      - May-Aug., (10 folders)
      - Sept.-Nov., (12 folders) (Box II:401)
      - Dec., (3 folders) (Box II:402)
    - Summit, United States and Soviet Union, Washington, D.C., (2 folders)
    - Supreme Court, (2 folders)
    - Surroundings
    - "S" miscellaneous, (2 folders); (7 folders) (Box II:403)
    - Television
    - "T-U" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Vietnam (Box II:404)
    - "V" miscellaneous
    - Waldheim, Kurt
    - Wyzanski, Charles E., (3 folders)
    - "W" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Yale University, New Haven, Conn.
    - Yugoslavia
    - "Y-Z" miscellaneous (Box II:405)
  - 1988
    - Abortion
    - Afghanistan
    - Africa
      - Angola, (2 folders)
      - Botswana
      - General
      - Mozambique, (2 folders)
      - Namibia
      - Somalia
      - South Africa
        - African National Congress
        - Disinvestment, (1 folder) (Box II:406)
        - Ford Foundation
        - General, (4 folders)
        - Law
        - Press, (3 folders)
        - United States (Box II:407)
      - Sudan
      - Zimbabwe
    - American Civil Liberties Union
    - "A" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Book reviews, (4 folders)
    - Bork, Robert H.
    - Boston, Mass.
    - Brennan, William J.
    - Bylines
    - "B" miscellaneous, (5 folders)
    - Capital punishment (Box II:408)
    - Censorship, (2 folders)
    - Central Intelligence Agency (Box II:409)
    - China
    - Committee to Protect Journalists, (2 folders)
    - Constitution, (2 folders)
    - Courts, (1 folder) (Box II:410)
    - Crime
    - Czechoslovakia
    - "C" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Defense
      - General
      - Nuclear weapons
        - General
        - Strategic Defense Initiative
        - Treaty
    - Drugs, (2 folders)
    - "D" miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box II:411)
    - Economy, (3 folders)
    - Education
    - "E" miscellaneous
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation, (2 folders)
    - France
    - Free speech, (2 folders)
    - Fund for Free Expression (Box II:412)
    - "F" miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Gideon's Trumpet, (3 folders)
    - Great Britain (Box II:413)
      - General
      - Trip
    - "G" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Harvard Magazine
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Human rights
    - "H" miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Immigration (Box II:414)
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Palestinians
      - Rafeedie, Fouad Yacoub, (2 folders)
    - International Foundation for the Survival and Development of Humanity
    - Iran-Contra Affair
      - Congress
      - General
      - North, Oliver
      - Special prosecutor (Box II:415)
        - Constitutionality of, (2 folders)
        - General, (2 folders)
    - Iraq
    - Ireland
    - Italy, trip
    - "I" miscellaneous